Hello again. You.
Are you ever going to tell me why you abandoned your own family?
Oh, come on, say it!
If you don't, you're gonna keep having this dream.
It's a reflection of the darkness inside of you.
I now dwell within you.
And I am.
I am the power.
Call for me when you feel like your spirit's breaking.
You must surrender yourself to me.
Then I can get you the revenge that you so desire.
Oh, and there's one last thing. Wake up you.
Finally.
It's about time I got the chance to kill some vampires.
Mika.
I don't want nobody to get killed.
I come and get you, I'm always ready to fight.
So don't take all of the blame where all is wet.
Always don't take all of the weight you always do.
There will always be something you cannot control.
We will overcome your salvation has begun.
No suns, no lights, such a mess all over.
Don't kill your wolves.
You make me realize who I need.
I'll be there, hold on, the changes somehow.
So where are you now?
I'll reach you.
Find out the shadows of the earth.
You lose your support.
The golden end is still wrong.
But I know it is a pain that makes us so human after all.
Toin and save you for the control.
About your precious worth.
This heart may respond to your call.
My, my, take a look at you.
That uniform looks awfully good on you.
Oh, thanks.
And you...
Oh, never mind.
You don't have to say it, I know what you're thinking.
You look dropped at gorgeous, Shinoa.
So, I thought we were meeting there.
Don't you want your orders?
Let's hear them.
Do you remember the vampires Gurren mentioned?
He wants us to go to Shinjuku to investigate.
Let me ask you this.
Are we gonna kill bloodsuckers when we get there?
We get it.
You hate vampires.
Enough with the blood lust.
Is that all you're interested in?
There's more to our job than just killing vampires.
Hey, are you listening?
But you're so boring.
I guess you don't want to survive once we get outside the wall.
Hmph.
We're from the Moon Demon Company.
We have orders beyond the wall.
Would you please let us out?
What?
There's no way.
That's an elite squad, right?
Yeah, it's no place for little kids.
Shut up.
They can hear you.
Hey, he just called you a kid.
How'd you like that?
They're talking about you.
Cause you're so short.
Whatever.
I won't be short forever.
I'm still blossoming.
My sister Mahiru was taller.
And she had the kind of rag that made all the boys lust after her.
Huh.
I didn't know you have a sister.
No, I had a sister.
Shino.
I'm sorry.
What?
You don't have a silly comeback for that one?
Okay.
Let's get going, you.
In a completely devastated world like this, it seems everybody's lost someone who's important to them.
It's just a way of life.
Lieutenant Colonel Gurren!
What in the hell is going on?
You wanna explain why I've been placed in a squad full of new recruits?
Who's that girl?
Who is she?
I've been in the extermination unit since I was 13 years old!
Maybe she's a new member like you.
I was 13 years old!
Let's find out.
Hey, wait up!
There you are!
Hey, you!
Would it kill you to be on time?
If I have to look at your ugly mug.
What's going on over there?
I could understand if you had made me team leader in charge of the noobs, but you chose her!
You've gotta be kidding me!
Do you seriously think Shinoah Haragi is more qualified than I am?
Well, well.
Look who's here.
You!
How dare you, Shinoah!
You're no team leader!
Sorry, Mitsu.
But Gurren thinks I'm right for the job.
Don't even think about it, Mitsuba.
From this day forward, Shinoah is your team leader, so I...
Don't worry, Lieutenant Colonel.
I can handle Mitsuba's temper.
After all, I'm a mature woman.
The whining of an incompetent loser doesn't affect me one bit.
I'll destroy you!
I hope that you ladies like solitary confinement.
Cause that's where you're headed if you keep this up.
I'll behave.
Yeah, I will do.
I'm gonna take a different route to Shinjuku, but I'll meet you there.
Before I go, let me make one thing clear.
The Moon Demon Company squads move in a five-man formation.
That's why Mitsuba's here.
We've found that five is the golden number when facing armed vampires.
Any more than that and attacks can get confusing.
Any less and we start losing troops.
So I want the five of you to stick together.
I don't want any more infighting while one of you idiots trying to fly solo.
Is that clear?
As crystal, sir.
Hear that?
Mr. Reckless behavior?
Hmph.
I can't promise anything.
If I come face to face with a vamp, I may just have to...
What's your problem?
Oh, wow.
Quick reflexes, kid.
Now I get it, Lieutenant Colonel Gurren.
You put me on this squad so I could train the new recruits.
Consider it dead, sir.
What are they gonna learn from a troublemaker?
Since when have I ever caused you any trouble?
Oh, man.
That girl is a pain in the ass.
For real.
Oh, wow.
If you're calling someone a pain in the ass, they must be pretty bad.
You say something?
Nope.
Not me.
Nuh-uh.
Did her kick hurt?
Kinda.
I'm okay.
Listen up.
Your fellow squad members are now your comrades, got it?
That means they're more important than family.
Protect them with your life.
Okay.
Are you ready for your first mission?
I want the five of you to head to Harajuku.
According to our intel, there's a growing vampire settlement there.
Crush them and free the people there holding hostage.
Then head north to Shinjuku.
This place is a wreck.
I barely remember what it used to look like anymore.
I haven't been outside the wall since I've been in the demon army's custody.
Before you and Kamizuki joined our General Ed class, you used to patrol the outside as guards, didn't you?
That's right.
It sucked.
You think you're tough just because you killed a couple of four horsemen of Jonth right outside the spell-protected wall?
Anybody could do that, loser.
The ones near the wall are weak, but once you get a half mile out or more, they're ruthless.
They're much stronger than anything you've ever fought back at headquarters.
You better be ready for the fight of your lives.
If you're not, then leave now.
We can't afford to have any weaklings in our squad, you hear me?
One little slip and we're all dead, so stay alert.
No chit-chatting and don't break formation.
Amateurs.
Is she always like this?
Could she be any more adorable?
Seems she's feeling the pressure of responsibility.
She doesn't want you dying on her watch.
It's a Rajaku station.
Well, this is the spot.
Yeah. Now how are we supposed to find the vampires?
A four horsemen of Jon!
Damn it!
What do you think you're doing?
Helping!
Don't break formation.
Someone help!
We gotta go and save her!
Come on!
That monster's gonna kill her!
Shut up!
What good's the vampire extermination unit if we can't even save one kid?
Let go of me!
Can't you see this is one of their traps?
As soon as we go out to save her, they'll attack and we'll all be dead.
I'm willing to put my life on the line.
Let me save her!
Forget it! We're gonna stand by!
Are you really gonna let that little girl die?
If you wanna stand by then so be it.
But I'm not abandoning anyone ever again!
Wait!
Oh no!
Don't move, Kamizuki!
The vampires are coming. We have to be on alert!
Wait!
Oh, no!
Don't move, Kameizuki.
The vampires are coming.
We have to be on alert.
The vampires are using her as bait to lure us out.
Are you sure?
Because that doesn't make sense.
The Four Horsemen of John have no will of their own.
So why would they obey the vampires?
They're not obeying.
They only kill humans.
They're simply following their natural instincts.
It's as if they were created to keep humanity's population under control.
Go, now!
You're dead!
Here come the vamps!
See?
I told you.
They release bait for the monsters.
And then attack the humans who try to help.
That was too easy.
It's the oldest vampire trick in the book.
Heads up, kid!
Don't look away at you!
Bless me your power.
Watch for the murder!
So strong. Who's here?
Yakuya!
You left yourself wide open, dumbass.
Oh, wow. Thanks, guys. You saved me.
How do they have cursed gear?
They're the vampire extermination unit.
Call for backup. I'll bet we can capture them.
No way.
All right, that's enough. Now, I think we should retreat.
Go right ahead. Run from the butcher, livestock.
What the hell did you call us?
Let's fall back. Ain't gonna happen.
Let them go, you. We're behind enemy lines. We need to leave before their backup gets here.
Okay, fine.
How could you be so stupid? Your reckless behavior put our entire squad in danger.
You're lucky those vampires only had second-class weapons. Otherwise, we'd be...
Look, I'm sorry. I should have followed orders.
But I don't regret what I did. That girl would have been dead if it wasn't for me.
Go ahead. Punch me as much as you want.
If it'll make you feel better.
But I would do it all over again.
You're an idiot. I hate people like you more than anything.
You're impulsive and stubborn.
You would put your whole squad in danger.
Excuse me?
Thanks for saving me.
Hey, don't mention it. I was just doing my job, that's all.
Don't worry. You're in good hands now.
The Japanese Imperial Demon Army is going to keep you safe.
Okay.
Just so you know, I hate your guts!
Huh?
Don't let her get to you.
Everyone in Moon Demon Company has a bit of a troubled past.
And our friend Mitsuba is no exception.
Hold up.
What does that mean?
Like I would tell you.
What's with that Yuichiro Hyakuya guy?
Ignoring orders and flying solo.
I can't believe the Lieutenant Colonel was dumb enough to let that tongue get into the Moon Demon Company.
Huh!
At first, they were like two rams butting heads.
But it wasn't long before they started to fall in love.
With him?
No way!
Do you really hate him that much?
Of course I do.
I hate anyone who would put their comrades at risk.
He upsets you because he reminds you of yourself back in the day, doesn't he?
Stay here!
How many times have I told you not to break formation?
I don't give a crap about formation.
Our comrade's about to die!
I did it!
You idiot!
What did I do?
Hurry!
Get out of here!
It wasn't your fault.
You did everything you could in your situation.
What happened that day had nothing to do with you breaking formation needs.
Shinoa.
Yeah?
Don't ever come in while I'm showering again.
Oh, come on!
Don't be so shy!
What?
No!
I can't tell if they're giggling or fighting.
If you don't mind, there's something important that I'd like to ask you about.
Cool?
We want to save other people.
Do the vampires have a lair, and if so, where can we find it?
It's okay.
You don't have to tell us anything if you don't want to.
We understand.
Goodness!
I feel so refreshed!
Yeah, I bet you do, perv.
I don't mind telling.
I want to show my appreciation.
Don't worry about that.
It's not a big deal.
You must be scared, and I don't blame you one bit.
You don't have to tell us just because we saved you.
Dumbass.
It's a mota-san, though.
That's where you'll find the vampire's lair.
According to the girl, vampires have a lair in the Amote-Sando subway station.
She said they're actually raising human children there.
Question.
Yes?
What is it, Kamizuki?
What are we going to do about the civilians they captured?
We'll ignore them for now.
They're not our priority on this mission.
We've got bigger things to worry about.
What's that look for?
If you've got a problem, you can go back to Shiba yet.
Nope, no problems here.
As long as I get to kill bloodsuckers, I'm good.
Okay, everyone.
Stay alert.
Also, if the vampires are awake and armed when we go in, we'll have to retreat.
We're going to retreat again?
This is it.
To be honest, you guys might be able to fend off the vampires on your own since you have
the Black Demon series, but that's dangerous, so I think it'd be best for us to stick together.
Be careful.
And whatever you do, don't break from any-
Yeah, yeah, I won't.
At least you recognize I could do it alone.
That's enough for me.
All right, team.
Let's move out.
Come and break it down for me.
I'm really well for
気がない星でも
願いなさず
最低最強割いた
夜更しが
奏でたいと
ただ
next time on Seraph of the End
first extermination
the cold
Okay.
You for the end of the night
escyang
And
it'll be
a little Repin'
tombs
but
I'll rings
soon
to
be
I'll know